Brain Research Institute. Annual reports. 1961-1986.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Brain Research Institute. Annual reports.
1961-1986
University Archives Record Series 195
UCLA Library Special Collections
4.6 linear ft. (4 boxes, 3 cartons)
Record Series 195 contains annual reports generated by UCLA's Brain Research Institute.
University of California, Los Angeles. Brain Research Institute.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 195 contains annual reports generated by UCLA's Brain Research Institute. Files include annual reports and completed information request forms.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3520383
- Annual Reports - #1, 2., 1961-1963. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports - #3, 4., 1963-1965. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports - #5, 6., 1965-1967. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Annual Reports - #7, 8., 1967-1969. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports - #9, 10., 1969-1971. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports - #11, 12., 1971-1973. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Annual Reports - #13, 14., 1973-1975. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Annual Reports - #15, 16., 1975-1977. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports - #17, 18., 1977-1979. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports - #19, 20., 1979-1981. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Annual Reports - #21, 22., 1981-1983. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports - #23, 24., 1983-1985. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports - #25, 26., 1985-1986. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-F., 1969-1970. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - G-M., 1969-1970. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - N-S., 1969-1970. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - T-Z., 1969-1970. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-E., 1971-1972. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - F-N., 1971-1972. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - O-R., 1971-1972. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - S-Z., 1971-1972. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-E., 1972-1973. (Box 5, Folder 9)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - F-M., 1972-1973. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - N-S., 1972-1973. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - T-Z., 1972-1973. (Box 5, Folder 12)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-E., 1973-1974. (Box 5, Folder 13)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - F-L., 1973-1974. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - M-R., 1973-1974. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - S-Z., 1973-1974. (Box 5, Folder 16)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-F., 1975-1976. (Box 5, Folder 17)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - G-M., 1975-1976. (Box 5, Folder 18)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - N-S., 1975-1976. (Box 5, Folder 19)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - T-Z., 1975-1976. (Box 5, Folder 20)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-E., 1976-1977. (Box 5, Folder 21)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - F-M., 1976-1977. (Box 5, Folder 22)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - N-S., 1976-1977. (Box 6, Folder 1)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - T-Z., 1976-1977. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-F., 1977-1978. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - G-M., 1977-1978. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - N-S., 1977-1978. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - T-Z., 1977-1978. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-E., 1978-1979. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - F-L., 1978-1979. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - M-R., 1978-1979. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - S-Z., 1978-1979. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-F., 1979-1980. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - G-L., 1979-1980. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - M-S., 1979-1980. (Box 6, Folder 13)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - T-Z., 1979-1980. (Box 6, Folder 14)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-C., 1980-1981. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - D-H., 1980-1981. (Box 6, Folder 16)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - I-O., 1980-1981. (Box 6, Folder 17)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - P-U., 1980-1981. (Box 6, Folder 18)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - V-Z., 1980-1981. (Box 6, Folder 19)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-C., 1981-1982. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - D-G., 1981-1982. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - H-L., 1981-1982. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - M-R., 1981-1982. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - S-Z., 1981-1982. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - A-C., 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - D-H., 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - I-O., 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 8)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - P-U., 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- BRI Annual Report - Information Request Forms, Completed - V-Z., 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 10)